hipswap.com 2016-11-06

# HipSwap Privacy Policy | HipSwap

Updated: May 14, 2012

This Privacy Policy covers the website [www.HipSwap.com](http://www.hipswap.com/ "www.HipSwap.com") (the "Site") and all services and applications (together, the "Service") provided by HipSwap, Inc. ("HipSwap" "we" "our" or "us"). We take privacy very seriously and we will not use or share your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy.

**Information Collection and How it is Used**

Our primary goals in collecting information are to provide and improve our website, services, applications, features and content, and to administer your membership.

**Personally Identifiable Information:** When you register to become a HipSwap member, when you choose to post an item for "sell, swap or free," or when you wish to contact another HipSwap member, we will ask you for personally identifiable information, such as your first name and e-mail address. Your name and other information you choose to add to your profile will be available for public viewing on the Service. We may use your email address to send you Service-related notices. We may also send you newsletters, marketing or promotional materials and other information that may be of interest to you. If you do not want to receive such messages, you may opt out by following the instructions in the message.

**Log Files:** When you use the Service, our servers automatically record certain information that your web browser or mobile device sends whenever you visit any website or use any mobile application. These server logs may include information such as your web request, Internet Protocol ("IP") address, browser type, referring / exit pages and URLs, number of clicks, domain names, landing pages, pages viewed, and other such information.

**Cookies:** When you visit the Site, we may send one or more "cookies" - small data files - to your computer to uniquely identify your browser and let HipSwap help you log in faster and enhance your navigation through the site. A cookie may convey anonymous information about how you browse the Site, but does not collect personal information about you. A persistent cookie remains on your computer after you close your browser so that it can be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the Site. Persistent cookies can be removed by following your web browser's directions. A session cookie is temporary and disappears after you close your browser. You can reset your web browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some features of the Service may not function properly if the ability to accept cookies is disabled.

**Web Beacons:** When you use the Service, we may employ clear GIFs which are used to track the online usage patterns of our users anonymously. No personally identifiable information from your HipSwap account is collected using these clear GIFs. In addition, we may also use clear GIFs in HTML-based emails sent to our users to track which emails are opened by recipients. The information is used to enable more accurate reporting and make HipSwap better for our users.

**Third Party Services:** HipSwap may use Google Analytics to help understand use of the Service. Google Analytics collects the information sent by your browser as part of a web page request, including cookies and your IP address. Google Analytics also receives this information and their use of it is governed by their Privacy Policies.

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**

HipSwap is designed to allow information sharing by sellers and buyers, and people who swap items with each other to facilitate local in-person transactions. Items posted by sellers or swappers (the "Users"), ratings and reviews of sellers, buyers, and people who swap items, and the profile information of sellers, buyers, and people who swap items are visible to any visitor to the site. When you register to be a member on HipSwap, you create a profile page, including your first name and photo only. We will display your Profile Information in your profile page and elsewhere on the Site. We encourage users to think carefully about what information about themselves they disclose in their profile pages. You can review and revise your profile information at any time.

If you list an item for "sell, swap or free," we may publish that listing anywhere on the Site and may publish your listing on third party sites to increase distribution. We may also display the geographical location of your listing in the form of a map so that potential buyers can see the general area and neighborhood of your item, but your actual street address will not be disclosed.

**Changing or Deleting Account Information**

If you are a registered user of the Service, you may access and update or correct the information you provided to us by logging into your account. If you would like to remove your records from our system, please follow the instructions given on [this page](http://www.hipswap.com/about/sell).

**Security**

HipSwap uses commercially reasonable physical, managerial, and technical safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of your personal information. We cannot, however, ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to HipSwap or guarantee that your information on the Service may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, technical, or managerial safeguards.

In the event that personal information is compromised as a result of a breach of security, HipSwap will promptly attempt to notify those persons whose personal information has been compromised by email to the address provided in the applicable account.

**Changes to this Policy**

If we change our privacy policies and procedures, we will post those changes on this page to keep you aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances we may disclose it. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.

**Contacting Us**

If you have any questions about our practices or this privacy policy, please contact us at [privacy@HipSwap.com](mailto:privacy@HipSwap.com).
